<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Code Review on dubell.io</title><link>https://dubell.io/tags/code-review/</link><description>Recent content in Code Review on dubell.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 14:51:17 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dubell.io/tags/code-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Measuring attack paths in web applications</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2022/10/measuring-attack-paths-in-web-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 14:51:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2022/10/measuring-attack-paths-in-web-applications/</guid><description>Recently a customer asked us after our penetration test against their web application, the percentage of possible attack paths we had covered. It was a difficult question to answer because, a) the customer wanted us to focus on SQL injection and XSS (long story why) and b) it was a legacy application from 2003 containing a lot of code. The short answer I gave was that since the test was focused towards SQLi and XSS, naturally, some attack paths were not considered.</description></item><item><title>My thoughts on Secure Code Review</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2022/07/my-thoughts-on-secure-code-review/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 09:51:17 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2022/07/my-thoughts-on-secure-code-review/</guid><description>This article is going to cover my journey in cyber security, thoughts on secure code review and how to improve your own skills.
I have now worked for four years professionally in the cyber security field as consultant, mostly doing white-box assessments with access to source code. Since I have a developer background, I always approach a project with source code in mind, because to me, source is absolute truth. And from a customer perspective, it&amp;rsquo;s way more worth the money for me to be able to view the source in order to find deeper issues.</description></item></channel></rss>