<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CTF on dubell.io</title><link>https://dubell.io/categories/ctf/</link><description>Recent content in CTF on dubell.io</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dubell.io/categories/ctf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hack The Box - Olympus Writeup</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2019/08/htb-olympus-writeup/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2019/08/htb-olympus-writeup/</guid><description>I begun by scanning the box to find some interesting ports.
PORT STATE SERVICE VERSION
22/tcp filtered ssh
53/tcp open domain (unknown banner: Bind)
80/tcp open http Apache httpd
2222/tcp open ssh (protocol 2.0) Port 80 was open so I visited the site and found a picture of the almighty God Zeus. I checked the response headers in the developer console and noticed the xdebug variable. According to my google fu, it&amp;rsquo;s a PHP debugger which among other things, can be used to debug remote PHP applications.</description></item><item><title>SEC-T CTF - G1bs0n Writeup</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2017/09/sec-t-ctf-g1bs0n-writeup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2017/09/sec-t-ctf-g1bs0n-writeup/</guid><description>Hacking the gibson, one byte at the time&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>UIUCTF - Are we out of the woods yet? Reversing 350p</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2017/04/uiuctf-are-we-out-of-the-woods-yet-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2017/04/uiuctf-are-we-out-of-the-woods-yet-2/</guid><description>It looks like this python script was run through a custom packer. It&amp;#39;s just Python*, which means it must be easy to reverse, right?
*v3.6.1:69c0db5
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y8qQsXpcZXA This was fun little challenge that our team (https://chalmersctf.se) solved together. You are presented with the file packed.py that contains the following code:
import marshal, zlib, base64, itertools
def xor_strings(_left, _k):
out = b&amp;#39;&amp;#39;
for l, r in zip(_left, itertools.cycle(_k)):
out += (l ^ ord(r)).</description></item><item><title>VolgaCTF - Bloody Feedback writeup</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2017/03/volgactf-bloody-feedback-writeup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2017/03/volgactf-bloody-feedback-writeup/</guid><description>Bloody Feedback
Send your feedback at bloody-feedback.quals.2017.volgactf.ru
DO. NOT. USE. SQLMAP
Otherwise your IP will be banned The challenge basically has two functions, 1) Send feedback and 2) view the status of the sent feedback. There is also page that cotains &amp;ldquo;Top Messages&amp;rdquo; which is the feedback people send in. When you send feedback you get a token back which you can use to see if the feedback has been processed or not.</description></item><item><title>VolgaCTF - Share Point writeup</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2017/03/volgactf-share-point-writeup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2017/03/volgactf-share-point-writeup/</guid><description>Share Point
Look! I wrote a good service for sharing your files with your friends, enjoy)
share-point.quals.2017.volgactf.ru The challenge begun by signing in to the control panel by simply entering random account details. Once logged in you had the ability to upload files and share them with an other user. Since the site only had one functionality, uploading files, I assumed the goal had to be to upload a web shell and find the flag on the file system.</description></item><item><title>Chalmers CTF</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2017/02/chalmers-ctf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2017/02/chalmers-ctf/</guid><description>Hey, long time since last post, been busy with university and starting Chalmers very first CTF team: Chalmers CTF!!
Check out our website for information: https://chalmersctf.se</description></item><item><title>SEC-T CTF - Confusion Writeup</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2016/09/sec-t-ctf-confusion-writeup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2016/09/sec-t-ctf-confusion-writeup/</guid><description>This time I participated in the SEC-T CTF event and it was pretty fun! I played with a group of people from my university and we managed to get quite some points. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to solve some of the challenges on time. However this didn&amp;rsquo;t stop from trying to solve them once the event was over!
One of the challenges I was hooked on was called Confusion. The reason why was because it seemed like an &amp;ldquo;easy&amp;rdquo; challenge but for some reason I couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure it out!</description></item><item><title>Securityfest CTF - Defacer Challenge Writeup</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2016/06/securityfest-ctf-defacer-challenge-writeup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2016/06/securityfest-ctf-defacer-challenge-writeup/</guid><description>I actually learned something entirely new on this challenge, I decided I had to do a writeup to share my findings.
If you read my previous Securityfest CTF writeup you perhaps know that these challenges were from securityfest held in Sweden, which I attended. I did not solve this particular challenge on time in order to win any prizes, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me from trying to solve it.
The challenge is to get the flag by defacing this website http://alienzon.</description></item><item><title>Securityfest CTF - Coresec challenge writeup</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2016/06/securityfest-ctf-coresec-challenge-writeup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2016/06/securityfest-ctf-coresec-challenge-writeup/</guid><description>This challenge was produced by Coresec Systems and was released during Securityfest. I would liked to have spent more time on it during the event but couldn&amp;rsquo;t really find any time for it. Now the event is over and first year of university is completed, I decided to try to finish the challenge. It was quite tricky at some points but now when I think about it in hindsight, the challenge itself was actually fairly simple.</description></item><item><title>LogRhythm's Blackhat challenge - Write up</title><link>https://dubell.io/www/2015/08/logrhythms-blackhat-challenge-write-up/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dubell.io/www/2015/08/logrhythms-blackhat-challenge-write-up/</guid><description>For Blackhat 2015, LogRhythm Labs had a forensics contest for analyzing a .pcap file and finding the secret missile launch code. Find the password and enter the contest to win one of these:
I really wanted to win this!
Analyzing the PCAP with WireShark I downloaded the .pcap file and loaded it into wireshark. I begun by checking the Protocol Hierarchy under Statistics to get a view on the protocols used.</description></item></channel></rss>